吸血鬼后裔  前情提要  兰德勒拿着一把刀
Previously on Legacies... ALARIC: Landon took a knife.
现在  本不该出现的怪物们
Now monsters that shouldn't exist have been
都紧随那把刀而来
coming after it ever since.
你被马里瓦尔耗尽了吗
CLARKE: You've been consumed by Malivore?
你所有朋友都忘记了
All your friends have forgotten
你曾经存在过
you ever existed.
马里瓦尔不想我在这儿
HOPE: Malivore doesn't want me here.
祝你好运  克拉克
Good luck, Clarke!
你跟我说怪物袭击已经停止了
You told me that the monster attacks had stopped,
然后  就在我出现之时
and then, right when I show up,
这些事就又开始了么
things start happening again?
我很确定自己就是这一切的罪魁祸首
I'm pretty sure I'm the reason.
我知道你不记得了
I know you don't remember this.
现在我这边就你最像一个父亲了
You're the closest thing I have to a father now.
没关系的  我们一起解决
It's okay. We'll figure it out together.
我知道你在里面  拉斐
LANDON: I know you're in there,.
我们会想办法把你变回来的
We're gonna find a way to get you back,
然后一切又会完好如初了  好吗
and then everything will be good again, okay?
他变成狼的时间越长  人性泯灭得就越多
The longer he's a wolf, the less human he'll be.
什么时候狼不需要人类好朋友了
And at what point does a wolf no longer need a human best friend?
也许他向前看了  因为他看到了
Maybe he moved on, 'cause he saw that you have someone
有人能让你
who can help you be
快乐
happy.
睡不好吗  差不多
Rough night? Yeah, actually.
感情问题  我爱上了一个
Uh, relationship trouble. Fell for a guy
根本都不知道我的存在的人
who doesn't even know that I exist.
你肯定是新来的  我还以为所有新生
Uh, you must be new. I thought I knew all
我都认识呢
of the incoming students.
这是什么学校
Oh, this is a school of some kind?
- 等等  你叫什么  - 塞巴斯蒂安
Wait. What's your name? Sebastian.
- 我叫丽兹  - 很高兴认识你  伊丽莎白
I'm Lizzie. It's good to meet you, Elizabeth.
老师们等着见您呢  瓦德摩斯教授
DORIAN: The faculty are waiting to meet you, Professor Vardemus.
叫我校长
Call me "Headmaster."
我看见你在同学身上施的那个小咒语了
I saw that little spell you cast on your classmate.
攻击魔法作为工具有其应有的作用
Offensive magic is a tool that has its place.
我为高年级学生
I'm creating a new magic curriculum
开了一门新的魔法课  我希望第一个选课的人是你
for advanced students. I'd like you to be the first.
好了伙计们  我们开始吧
All right boys, let's do this.
今年别再拼错了啊
And don't screw up the spelling this year.
屌这个词里面就一个i
There's one "I" in dick.
那可能指的就是你了
Probably should be a you.
你这是在侮辱我吗
Was that an insult?
我说不好  丹尼斯
I don't know, Dennis.
等你想明白  记得告诉我啊
Let me know when you figure it out.
我们为什么要这么做呢
Why are we doing this?
因为一向如此啊
Because we always do.
我们每年都给塞尔瓦托学校搞破坏
We vandalize the Salvatore School every year.
这是传统
It's tradition.
选举学院也是咯
So is the electoral college.
没听说过他们
Never heard of 'em.
他们的橄榄球队一定很差
Football team must suck.
你们还等什么呢
What are y'all waiting for?
我告诉过你们任务了
I told you what to do.
我没记错的话  是四分位发号施令
Last I checked, QB calls the plays.
要我说我们回家吧
I say we go home.
我也没记错的话  我已经
The last I checked, I've been starting
开始做线卫有四年了
at linebacker for four years now.
你是四分位只是
And you're only our quarterback
因为康纳转学了还是怎么的
because Connor transferred or something.
不止这个原因
Not the only reason.
上帝在我的右臂里倾注了雷电之力
God also put a thunderbolt in my right arm.
在我揍你之前  还是赶紧走吧
So let's just go before you experience it.
这是我的车
It's my truck,
我哪都不去
and I ain't going anywhere.
那你就动手啊  索尔
So do what you got to do, Thor.
反正  今天晚上散步挺开心的
Nice night for a walk, anyway.
祝你好运  丹尼斯
Good luck with the spelling, Dennis.
嘿  你俩要去哪啊
Hey, where are you two going?
一对基佬
Pansies.
要是能逮只狼  今晚也不算白过了
Night won't be a waste if I can bag a wolf.
吸血鬼后裔
第2季   第3集
擦枪字幕组
XGunSubTeam
原创
译制
mcar.cc
荣誉
出品
合作洽谈     Q:864413459
他们说爱过  再失去  也总比
HOPE: They say that it's better to have loved and lost
没有爱过要好
than never to have loved at all.
不管是谁写的这句话  显然他们
Whoever wrote that clearly never experienced
都没经历过会
the love of their life
忘记他们存在的那种爱
forgetting their whole existence.
这就让你想一个人生活
It makes you want to be alone,
因为不曾拥有过  又何谈失去呢
because you can't lose what you never had.
翻 译  silver
快点  走了
YOUNG MAN: Come on, let's go!
翻 译  moonpie
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
翻 译  RossyGeng
看上去不言而喻了
This looks pretty self-explanatory,
翻 译  十二点要睡觉
不过你想试试么
but you want to give it a shot?
有毒的男生和过时的体育生恶作剧混合在一起吗
Um, toxic masculinity mixed with outdated sports pranks?
不可能是霍普干的
There's no way Hope did it.
她是森林狼  不是种马
She's a Timberwolf, not a Stallion.
玛雅  出什么事了
Maya? What happened?
别担心  她是我妈
Oh, don't worry. She's my mom.
翻 译  霸气小肥鹅
我们确实不怎么喜欢谈
We don't really like to talk about it.
我们
We?
霍普  伊森
Hey, Hope. Ethan?
校 对   silver
所以你们是
So you guys are...?
特 效   麦 斯
他们都是我孩子  不论这身份会让他俩多尴尬
My kids, no matter how much it embarrasses them.
因为谁不想坐着
'Cause who doesn't like getting dropped off
警车上学啊
to school in a cop car?
我来是因为公事
I'm on official business.
现在  告诉我可以去哪找萨尔茨曼校长
Now... show me where I can find Principal Saltzman.
抱歉  我没见过他
Yeah, sorry, I... I haven't seen him.
如我所说  我刚到这里
Like I said, I'm pretty new here.
他的队友最后一次见到他
Well, his teammates last saw him
是在萨尔茨曼的老磨坊
at the Old Mill, by the Salvatore School.
我们发现他的车扔在那里  在附近还发现了他的猎枪
We found his truck abandoned, and his hunting rifle nearby.
好的  我会跟他的同学还有各位老师确认一下
Okay. Well, I will check with his classmates and his teachers.
我也希望能有所帮助  但如我所说
I wish I could be more helpful, but like I said,
我还在了解这些学生呢
I'm still getting to know the students.
还有警长
And the sheriff.
我和老警长是朋友
I was friends with the old one.
拜托  别再跟我讲多诺万警长的光辉事迹了
Please, no more stories about how great Sheriff Donovan was.
他的形象已经够高大的了
His shoes are already big enough.
自我从城市搬来以后  这是我第一个真正意义上的案子
And this is my first real case since I moved from the city.
说实话  我完全不介意自己现在
Truthfully, I didn't mind that my biggest concern
这个节骨眼上最担心的是狗群失踪
up to this point was a rash of missing dogs.
也许它们有所关联
Maybe they're connected.
可能吧
Maybe.
我把电话留给你
I'll leave you my phone number.
有情况随时叫我
Call me anytime.
我们俩聊天你是都听到了吗
Did you get all that?
没错
Yeah.
- 她对你相当有兴趣啊  - 什么
She's definitely into you. What?
不  才不是  她只是因为新来镇上  想交点朋友而已
No. No, she's just new to town, trying to make friends.
你就正需要交点朋友
Which is exactly what you need to be doing.
这个我去年就试过了
Yeah, well, tried that last year.
不过没解决呢
Didn't really work out.
所以我要将重心都放在猎杀怪物上
So I'm gonna focus on monster slaying.
听起来似乎可能有另一个怪物
Well, it sounds like there could be another monster
在萨尔瓦托高中附近游荡
lurking around the Salvatore School.
我会联系一下多利安
So I'll check in with Dorian,
因为他有我们没有的研究权限
since he has access to research we don't.
还有什么别的主意吗
Any other ideas?
就一个  不过
Just one, but, uh...
你我都不会喜欢的
we are both going to hate it.
塞尔瓦托寄宿学校
众所周知
VARDEMUS: As you are well aware,
现在到了一年一度的与神秘瀑布镇高中
it's time for the annual American football match
进行橄榄球比赛的时候了
with Mystic Falls High.
太好了
Great.
今天  你们不用为了满足人类的优越感
Today, you will not be forced to lose a game
而被迫输掉比赛
so that humans can feel superior.
你们每一个人都是特别的
Every one of you is special.
每一个人
Every one of you.
是时候大展身手了
And it's time you showed it.
怎么做
How?
通过适度使用你们的能力  萨尔茨曼小姐
By using your powers in moderation, Ms. Saltzman.
目的不在于曝光
The goal is not exposure,
只是为了赢得比赛
merely to win.
可以把这当做是一种控制练习
Think of it as an exercise in control.
我就等这一刻呢
Well, I am here for it.
在去年之后  那种向森林狼
After last year, it'll feel really good
展示我们自身全部实力的感觉真是太好了
to show those Timberwolves what we're all about.
对吧
Right?
这次比赛让谁作为你们的四分位带队
And who better to lead you in this endeavor,
更好一些呢
as your quarterback,
还有比兰德勒·卡比更合适的人选吗
than our own Landon Kirby?
我们有紧急情况
We have an emergency.
瓦德摩斯校长想让兰德勒担任四分位
Headmaster Vardemus wants Landon to play QB.
好啊
Cool.
挺好  那可是你的位置啊
Cool? That's your slot.
今年我在找寻更大的游戏
I'm hunting bigger game this year.
你暗恋的那个塞巴斯蒂安兄弟吗
That Sebastian dude you're crushing on?
要是他不是男的怎么办
What if he's not a dude at all?
我昨晚就在想这事
I was thinking about it last night.
他露面的方式
Him just showing up the way he did
十分可疑
was super fishy.
鉴于我们学校去年出过的事
Given the events of our last school year...
怪物概览
Compendium Monstrum?
你觉得他是怪物吗
You think he's a monster?
我是觉得不能排除这种可能
I'm thinking I can't rule it out.
抱歉  但这事远比橄榄球要重要
So, sorry, but this is way more important than football.
即便橄榄球我很在行吧
Even though I'm awesome at it.
兰德勒曾经拉伤过腹股沟
Well... Landon pulled his groin
摔的那个惨
combing his hair once.
我们需要你参加比赛
We need you at that game.
MG  这可能是我生平第一次
MG, I am mentally healthy for perhaps
心理健康  准备好恋爱
the first time in my life, and ready for romance.
希望我和塞巴斯蒂安能成
I'm hoping that Sebastian pans out.
但如果他不行的话  我就得
But if he doesn't, I need to set my sights
另寻他人了
on someone else.
比说  谁呢
Like, uh... ...who?
第一个问我的人咯
The first person that asks.
今天是不会拒绝的一年  还记得吗
It's the year of yes. Remember?
那样的话  两双眼
Well, in that case, two sets of eyes
总比一双眼睛强吧  尤其是其中一双
are better than one, especially when one of them
还会吸血鬼速读呢  所以来参加比赛吧
can vamp-read, so come to the game.
我帮你读这本书  然后我们就可以甘清楚
I'll help you hit the books, and we can figure out who
那个人到底是什么东西了
and what this guy really is.
我有点担心可能发现的东西
Part of me is worried about what we might find out.
你应该说同意  记得吗
You're supposed to say yes. Remember?
好吧  我同意
Fine. Yes.
估计我最好得把装秋衣的那个垃圾袋找出来了
Guess I better go dig up that trash bag of a jersey.
准备
LANDON: Yellow 80.
Yellow 80...
抱歉我有点心不在焉
Sorry.
寄养家庭没有过橄榄球队
Foster care didn't have a football team.
还记得我跟你说的吗  我就是个傻逼
What did I tell you? I'm a total fraud.
现在全校都会知道了
Now the whole school's gonna see it, and...
简直太糟糕了
this is a total disaster.
就像我说过的
And like I told you,
我很会照看人的
I'm really good at taking care of people.
- 我们会一起度过这个难关  - 怎么度过
- We're gonna get through this.- How?
我连投球都不会
I can't even throw.
你当然会投了
Yes, you can.
只是需要一点点的帮助
You just need a little help.
全力以赴
Viribus.
你刚刚对我做了什么
What'd you just do?
你试试看
See for yourself.
卡莱布
Kaleb!
我靠
Damn!
这才是我四分卫该有的样子嘛
That's my quarterback.
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
时而肮脏  时而高尚
* Call me dirt or call me diamonds *
《Creature》- BONES UK
时而善良  时而残暴
* Call me crass or call me cruel *
不管怎样  叫我爸爸  - 你认识这个女孩吗
* Call me daddy... * Do you know that girl?
不算认识吧
Not really.
我们就只是
We just, uh...
一起喝了杯奶昔
shared a milkshake once.
赶紧速战速决
Let's just get this over with as fast as possible.
我也想  我比你还想尽快
Works for me. I'm no more comfortable
比完这场赛
being here than you are.
里克
Ric...
有点事情  你得过来看下
There's something that you need to see.
欢迎大家参加一年一度
Let us begin our annual rite
美式足球比赛
of American excess.
不过和去年不一样的是
But unlike last year,
我希望没有暴力行为
I expect no unseemly violence, only for each team
希望每个队伍都能用尽全力
to play to the fullest extent of their abilities.
都明白了吧
Understood?
神秘瀑布镇高中的森林狼队
Timberwolves of Mystic Falls,
或许
you may,
我想采用他们说的
as I believe they say,
抛硬币来决定
call it in the air.
我猜人头
Heads.
- 猜反面总没有错  - 我们来发球
- Tails never fails. - We'll take the ball.
比赛正式开始
So it begins.
对了  先握手示好
Uh, shake hands.
下次一起喝奶昔
Having another milkshake moment?
不了
Sorry.
我们发现他在树林里徘徊
We found him wandering the woods,
人是半疯的状态
half out of his mind.
直到我们叫他  才反应过来
He didn't settle down until we compelled him.
那他还记得什么吗
Does he remember anything?
告诉他你看到了什么  丹尼斯
Tell him what you saw, Dennis.
像是一种野兽
It was some kind of animal.
像是鬣狗和狼的杂交品种
Like a-a hyena mixed with a wolf,
有着大爪子
with huge claws.
它抓住了我
It grabbed me.
我以为它要吃了我
I thought it was gonna eat me,
不过他把我吐出来了
but then it spit me out.
有什么想法吗
Does that ring any bells?
我能找到的是一种叫山卡·华莱金的生物
Closest thing I could find was a Shunka Warakin.
到现在  还是美国的民间传说
Until this morning, it was a Native American myth.
简单来说  意思是夺走狗
Roughly translated, it means "carrying off dogs."
根据爱荷华传奇  丹尼斯太幸运了
Lucky for Dennis, according to Ioway legend,
它只吃狼人
all it eats are werewolves.
多利安发现了失踪的孩子
Dorian found the missing kid.
谢天谢地  他没事
Thank God he's okay.
不过我们也发现了其他的野兽
But we definitely have another monster
在树林间徘徊
wandering around these woods.
多利安深入调查了一下
Dorian's digging into the research,
他认为是山卡
but he thinks it's a Shunka.
- 那是什么  - 我知道你要问它是什么
What's... And before you ask what that is,
它是以狼人为食的肉食动物
it's a carnivorous creature that feeds only on werewolves.
幸好那天不是满月
Good thing it's not a full moon.
是呀  不过自从你走后
Yeah, except Raf has been stuck in wolf form
拉斐就一直困在狼的形态了
ever since you've been gone.
你说什么  拉斐
Wait, Raf?
我都不知道他变成狼了
I didn't even know that he turned. Yeah.
和三合会交战时的事
Happened fighting Triad.
从那以后就变不会正常人了
Hasn't been able to turn back since.
他当然变不回来了
Yeah, of course he can't turn back.
我是唯一能让他变回来的人
I'm the only one that can turn him back.
我就是那个给他那颗新月戒指的人
I'm the one that gave him that crescent moon ring.
好了  我得去找他
Okay, look, I've got to go find him
在山卡找到他之前
before the Shunka finds him first.
我来接球
I got it.
嗨了两晚
* I got two nights in a row *
还有一场派对
* Oh, we gon' put on a show *
- 怎么回事  - 牵着黑牛
What? * With the black bull in tow *
不要这个样子看着我
* Don't look at me like that. *
我要去找拉斐
I need to get out of here and find Raf.
我同意  得想办法
Agreed. We just need to find a way
从赛场上脱身
to ditch this game.
不行  拉斐尔的事情由我负责
No. Rafael is my responsibility.
你得待在这
You need to stay here and keep an eye
- 盯着新裁判  - 为什么
on that new headmaster. Why?
他用魔法做了弊
Because he already used magic to cheat.
他肯定有猫腻
He's up to something.
卡罗琳替代了我的工作
Caroline picked my replacement herself.
她不可能会找个
There's no way that she's gonna hire a...
打伞的奇葩
...weirdo with an umbrella.
好  我知道了
Okay, I'm on it.
现在要悄咪咪地溜走了  祝我好运吧
Okay. Now to plot my escape. Wish me luck.
祝你好运
Break a leg.
我以为抢到她球了  结果  我猜她耍了小把戏
I thought I had her. Trick play, I guess.
你想不到吧  我们完蛋了
You have no idea. We're screwed.
就一分而已
Hey, it was just one score.
等下你就会在那肆意驰骋
And you're gonna march us straight down that field
带领我们
and tie us up.
你什么意思  你哥哥是四分卫吧
What do you mean? Your brother's the quarterback.
今天他不是我哥哥
No, not today.
他不会为了这个比赛
He can't risk blowing out his knee
冒膝盖受伤的风险
on some pick-up game, so...
我们全指望你了
we're all counting on you.
上吧  你可以的
Come on. You got it.
你看到那场拦截了吗
Did you see that block?
我完全开启了橄榄球的新操作
I totally opened up the lane and sprung that play,
以很高逼格的方式
in a respectful way.
不好意思  正忙着搞清楚
Sorry, too busy figuring out
我是不是爱上了长毛动物
if I'm falling in love with a yeti.
然后呢
And?
没有结果
Inconclusive.
你本该帮我思考的
You're supposed to be helping me.
那我下场不比了  现在深入探讨这个问题
Okay, I'll take the next series off and dig in.
你真的太好了
You're a really great...
你太暖了  MG
You're just really great, MG.
我不知道没了你怎么办
I don't know what I'd do without you.
让我们先弄清楚该如何处理塞巴斯蒂安
Let's figure out what to do about Sebastian first.
再来担心我
Then we can worry about me.
小伙伴们  我们赢下这场比赛吧
Okay, uh, all right, guys, let's do this.
怎么做  你是四分卫  霍普
Do what? You're the quarterback, Hope.
你来指挥
You call the plays.
大家都跑远一点吗
Everybody go long?
我可以啊  数三秒大家打个气吧
Works for me. Timberwolves on three?
1  2  3  森林狼队最棒
One, two, three. ALL: Timberwolves!
我正在大城市生活  尽我所能
* I'm living the big city life, just doing what I can *
等在桌子旁  没错  我是为男人工作的
* To get by waiting tables, yeah, I'm working for the man *
不过最近  我觉得我的生活像是
* And you know, lately it's starting to feel awful like *
后脚着地一样的糟糕  - 你等下球一落地就投出去
* I'm always on the back foot... * You're blitzing on first down.
酷啊
Cool.
不过确切的说  那是什么意思
Uh, what does that mean, exactly?
就是说她抢球的那一秒
It means the second she snaps the ball,
你大喊突袭  然后你干掉奶昔小姐
you yell "blitz" and you bury Little Miss Milkshake.
是不是太气势汹汹了
* Yeah * That's aggressive.
你是不敢打她还是怎样
You have a problem hitting her or something?
她可不会心慈手软
She has no problem hitting on you.
想着她的突袭
Consider her blitzed.
感觉我总是后脚着地
* It feels like I'm always on my back foot *
看着来势汹汹啊
That's aggressive.
大家都会说我是个烂人
* Everybody says that I'm a slob... * Oh...
我就是个宇宙垃圾  而且超懒
* That I'm a waste of space and super lazy, oh, my God *
兰德勒  突袭
Landon! Oh, uh, blitz!
就在此时此地  工作睡觉
* I'll be right here, sleeping on the job *
等在桌子旁  为了68美元
* Getting paid six-eighty to wait on tables *
来自广东富婆和富狗狗们的小费
* Of rich ladies and their dogs *
真希望拿的钱能更多
* I wish that I had more than I got *
我拿到球了
I got it. I got it.
刚刚怎么回事
What was that?!
像岩石般的球
* And balling like The Rock, but you know *
不过最近  感觉糟糕透顶
* Lately, it's starting to feel awful like... *
投球太棒了吧  约翰尼·犹他手法
Hell of a throw, Johnny Utah.
没事吧
Are you okay? Uh-huh.
- 抱歉啊  - 没事
I'm so sorry. Oh, it's okay.
可能是刚刚扭到了吧
Um, yeah, I think it's just twisted. Yeah.
学校有护士站
Um, well, there's a nurse's office in the school.
一楼  右边
First floor, right inside.
好的
Okay.
你会找到的
You'll see it.
谢谢你  我能找到
Okay. Uh, I think I'll find it, thank you.
走吧  种马队
Let's go, Stallions, let's go...
看起来你需要一个新四分卫
Looks like you need a new quarterback.
狩猎愉快啊
Happy hunting.
刚才怎么了
What was that all about?
乔西  我撞到她了
Josie. I hurt her.
你没有  她很好  百分百装的
No, you didn't, she's fine. She was clearly faking.
为什么她要装受伤了呢
Why would she fake something like that?
你为什么胳膊肘往外拐
Why are you taking her side?
不是拐不拐的问题吧
It's not about sides.
就是正常人的思维啊
I'm just being a decent human being.
那你现在可不是正常人  你怕不是凤凰涅槃了吧
Well, you're not a human, you're a phoenix.
这就是你选择站哪队的比赛
This is a game where there are sides.
另外  她有问题
Plus, I mean, there's something off about her.
虽然我不知道什么事  不过肯定有事
- I just-- I don't know what, but there's something.
不止她一个
Yeah, she's not the only one.
打住  打住  你来是有任务的
Stop, stop, stop. You're here for a reason.
你在我的房间做什么
What are you doing in my room?
我知道这不对
Uh... look, I know that this looks bad... No.
这看起来是一种魔法
It looks like magic.
静止术
Corporis impetus!
我开始觉得你不是普通女孩了
I'm starting to think you're not some ordinary girl.
我叫霍普
Look, my name is Hope, okay?
我是个女巫
I-I'm a witch.
我和萨尔茨曼博士一起共事
I'm working with Dr. Saltzman.
他让我施个定位咒找到拉斐尔
He asked me to do a locater spell to find Rafael.
他怎么不让他自己女儿找呢
Why wouldn't he ask one of his own daughters?
因为她们不懂新月狼族
Because they don't know about the Crescent Wolf Clan.
不像我了解
Not like I do.
狼  我读到过
Wol-- I-I've read about that.
就是说你能让拉斐尔回来吗
Does that mean you can turn Raf back?
解除
Saeclum.
森林里有个怪兽  专吃狼人
There is a monster in the woods, and it feeds on werewolves.
那我和你一起去
Ooh. Then I'm coming with you.
抱歉  但我独自行动
Sorry, but I fly solo.
他是我最好的朋友
He's my best friend.
你知道我能再次定住你是吧
You do realize I could freeze you again, right?
这个咒是永久的吗
Would that spell last forever?
尽量跟上吧
Just try to keep up.
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器
好了好了  骏马队  我看到你们啦
Okay, okay, Stallions, I see you.
我说的就是  干得漂亮  同志们
That's what I'm talking about. Nice job, guys.
上半场不错
Good half. Now,
现在  我们放轻松
we can take it easy.
这比赛尘埃落定了
This game is done and dusted.
不  没有
Hey. No, it's not.
- 我们还要得更多分  - 我们都
- We need to score more. - We're up
35比7了  不用费劲了
35-7, Jo. No reason to rub it in.
听上去很酷
I mean, it sounded cool and all,
再和那帮人拼下去  没必要了
sticking it to the townies, but now it feels wrong.
下半场没有必要用我们自己的超能力了
I don't think we need to use our powers in the second half.
什么  为什么
What? Why not?
因为你爸说的没错
Because your dad was right
游戏就要正当的玩
about the way the game should be played.
很多事他都说的对
He was right about a lot of things.
但你已经知道我对这件事的感受了
But you already know how I feel about that subject.
你是不想打四分位了是吧
So, I'm guessing you don't want to play quarterback, then?
因为我觉得兰德勒不会回来了
Because I don't think that Landon's coming back.
得有人来替补
Someone needs to step up.
你是认真的吗
You serious?
我来
I'll do it.
无意冒犯  韦德  但你不行
No offense, Wade, but no.
如果我们不用超能力
If we're not gonna use our powers,
那我们得让旧魔法回来
we need the old magic back.
就这么定了
Pass.
休息够了
Enough leisure.
回到场上  展示你们的风采
Get back out there and showcase your superiority.
爸
Dad.
姑娘们
Hi, girls, uh,
我需要跟你们校长说两句
I just need a moment with your headmaster.
.
什么事  教练
What is it, Coach?
是萨尔茨曼校长
It's Principal Saltzman.
我知道你是谁  萨尔茨曼博士
I'm well aware of who you are, Dr. Saltzman.
事实上  正是因为你做回了博士
In fact, you being who you are
所以我才能接手你的校长工作
is why I have your old job.
我知道你在干嘛  你在让孩子们丢脸
Mm. I know what you're doing. You're embarrassing my kids.
下半场别再用超能力了
Now ease up in the second half.
你有没有想过  我的学生
Did you ever occur to you that my kids
就是比你的学生优秀呢
are simply superior to yours?
当然是的  显而易见
Of course they are. And it's obvious
他们在用魔法  这不公平
they're using their magic, and it isn't fair.
在他们眼中显而易见的是你和我
The only people to whom that's obvious are you and me,
所以我不觉得有什么问题
so I don't see the problem.
说清楚  不公平的
And to be clear, what wasn't fair
是你这些年一直压制他们的能力
was you stifling their abilities all these years.
我是在保护他们
I was trying to protect them.
那样有用吗
How did that work out?
你想怎样
What the hell is your deal? Hmm?
不说橄榄球比赛
Forget about football.
你到底在玩什么把戏
What game are you really playing?
祝你好运  教练
Best of luck, Coach.
希望你会需要
I anticipate you'll need it.
有好消息吗  多里安
Some good news, Dorian?
也许明年我来带比赛
Maybe next year I can coach the game
你来做怪物研究
and you can do the monster research.
与此同时  这有你要的好消息
In the meantime, here's that good news you asked for.
杀山卡的方法和杀其他怪物差不多
So, killing a Shunka is pretty much like killing anything else.
你要从心脏  喉咙  或大脑下手
You want to go for the heart, the throat or the brain.
- 听上去很容易啊  - 差不多  这玩意
- Sounds easy enough. - Kind of. It's bigger
比我想象的要大
than I thought.
有多大
How big?
跟你的卡车那么大
About the size of your truck.
它的兽皮很厚
And the hide's thick, too,
所以可能背后袭击最容易
so probably easiest to get it from the back.
幸亏你说了
Good to know.
- 还有别的吗  - 我还发现
- Anything else? - Yeah, I found
这有条奇怪的参考文献说它的叫喊声像人
this one weird reference that says it cries like a man.
不知道这是什么意思
Not sure what that means.
希望在我们发现之前它已经死了
Well, hopefully it'll be dead before we find out.
我会告诉霍普的
I'll let Hope know.
对  拉斐应该在前面了
Yeah, Raf should be up ahead.
- 好  - 并不好
- Cool. - Meaning not cool
抱歉  只是
Sorry. It's just...
没什么
nothing.
明明有话要说
Meaning something.
很蠢  但拉斐第一次变狼身之前
It's stupid, but when Raf was first stuck as a wolf,
他都和我一起玩的  但之后
he used to always hang out with me, but then he, like,
他就不这样了
he stopped.
就好像他忘了或者走了
Like, he forgot or he moved on.
你很担心
And you're worried
他变回人类时还会这样是吗
that it's gonna be the same when he's human again?
我都说了  这话很蠢
Told you it was stupid.
我不觉得蠢啊
I don't think it's stupid.
失去所爱的人很心痛的
It's painful to lose someone that you love.
是啊
Yeah.
这滋味我懂
Oh, I know all about that.
我在收容所长大的
I grew up in the foster system.
被寄宿在一个又一个家庭
Getting bounced around from family to family made me want
这让我排斥所有人  后来我才明白
to shut everybody out until I realized life's a lot harder
没人做你后盾  生活会更加艰辛
without someone watching your back.
相信我  兰德勒  你不必担心
Trust me, Landon, you don't have to worry
有人会忘记你
about anyone forgetting you.
救命  救命  来人啊
Help! Help! Somebody, help!
兰德勒  等等  回来  你不知道情况
Landon, wait, stay back. You don't know what's out there!
新氧
医美
专业医美APP
因为严谨  所以专业
新氧
医美
■
水光针补水
○
-
我猜得八九不离十
I have an educated guess.
我说了后退
I said stay back.
火球术
Incendia.
还有备用计划吗
Is there a plan "B"?
快告诉我还有备用计划
Please tell me there's a plan "B."
- 转身  - 为什么
- Turn around. - Why?
因为备用计划要关乎到我的裸体
Because plan "B" involves me getting naked.
- 什么  - 我要把它从你这引开
- What? - I have to draw it away from you.
为什么要裸体呢
Why does that require nudity?
因为这个怪物吃狼人
Because this monster feeds on werewolves.
但你不是女巫吗
But you're a witch.
是撒谎的女巫
A lying witch.
是撒谎又全裸的女巫
A lying, very naked witch.
我还不只是这样  我很想
Look, I'm more than that, and I wish I could stay
把一切都告诉你  但现在不行
and tell you all about it, but I can't.
所以我把它引开的时候
So when I draw this thing away from you,
我要你去找萨尔茨曼博士还有拉斐
I need you to go find Dr. Saltzman and Raf.
它为何会追你
Why would it after chase you...
原来你是个狼人女巫  我勒个去
Because you're a were-witch. Holy smokes.
我不是你要找的人  所以一边去吧
Not the droids you're looking for, so please move along.
你们在干嘛呢
What are you guys doing?
下半场就要开始了  我们缺个四分卫
The second half's about to start and we're down a QB.
你想试一下  投一把吗
You want to throw a bit, loosen up?
我更希望马上离开  让我打四分卫
I'd rather just leave now. I mean, there's no way
- 简直不可能  - 好啊
- that I'm playing quarterback. - Cool.
我正想上场呢
'Cause I was thinking I would.
我以为你害怕受伤呢
I thought you were worried about getting hurt.
那是种马队要担心的
The Stallions need to worry.
因为我们要用这个球
'Cause we're about to take this ball
和他们拼到最后达阵
and stick it in the end zone!
别问
Don't even ask.
少年汤姆·布兰迪要绝杀我们了
Okay, teenage Tom Brady is killing us.
你快上场吧  你打四分卫  我当外接手
So come ball out. You at QB, me at wide receiver.
咱俩配合
Hooking up.
全凭运动感觉
In a purely athletic sense.
我打四分位的时候美吗
Do I look pretty when I play quarterback?
你开玩笑吗
Are you kidding me?
你是我见过最美的人了
You are the hottest thing I've ever seen.
那就让我上场吧  教练
Then put me in, Coach.
既然你们似乎阻挡不了美国队长
Okay, since you guys can't seem to stop Captain America
也抢不到开球  我们的领先优势已逐渐消失
or not fumble a kickoff, our lead is bleeding
就像卡住的猪一样
like a stuck pig.
但别怕  我迷惑性很强
But fear not. I'm super absorbent.
这话什么意思啊
Wow. Uh, the hell's that supposed to mean?
意思是我们要假跑真传
It means we're gonna play-action,
所有犯规  抢球
all nines, bootleg left...
越位
...center deep cross.
做的以假乱真些  这是我的地盘
Make that a bootleg right.This is my onsite.
随便吧
Whatever.
只要我们能接球就行
As long as we're playing it straight.
那我干嘛啊
Uh, what do, what do I do?
你跑远点  韦恩  越远越好
You go long, Wayne. Real long.
- 我叫韦德  - 还是跑远点
- It's Wade, actually. You still go long.
好了  准备好了吗
All right. Ready?
加油
Break!
这次尽力抓好球
Just try and hold onto the ball this time.
他们会深入阵内  大家打起精神
They're gonna go deep. Keep your eyes open.
暴乱可能开始了
* Might start a riot... *
祸从口出  我不会住嘴的
* From my mouth, I won't be quiet *
直到你明白为止  一切都无所谓
* 'Cause everything is nothing till you realize *
是你想要的
* It's something you want... *
准备   就位
White 80. Set.
开始
Hut
我想来个痛快
* I want to lash out *
我想淋漓尽致
* I want to let it out *
我能感觉得到
* 'Cause I can feel it *
言语呼之欲出
* On the back of my tongue *
我忍不住
* Oh, hard to hold *
欲火在我心中
* This fire inside me *
我只知道
* All I know *
有时令人恐惧
* Is sometimes it's frightening... *
欲火在我心中
* This fire inside me... *
乔茜  我跟你说什么来着
Josie. What did I just tell you?
你以为我故意的吗
What, you think I did that on purpose?
我也想击败他们啊
I'm trying to bury these guys, too.
- 无所谓了  都不重要了  - 丽兹
- Whatever. None of this matters. - Lizzie.
你去哪
Where are you going?
交给我  不  MG  等等
I'm on it. No, MG, wait!
释放自己吧
* Out of the bottle *
释放吧
* Lash out. *
兰德勒
Landon!
Landon?
兰德勒
Landon!
听着  我真的很抱歉  早知道我是绝不会离开你的
Look, I'm sorry, I would have never left you.
我不知道它想要的是你
I didn't know that it wanted you.
拉斐  听着  我知道你不记得我了
Raf. Hey, look, I-I know you don't remember me,
但这都是我的错
but this is all my fault.
好吗  我绝不会让这样的事情
Okay? I would have never let anything like this
发生在你或者兰德勒身上的
happen to you or Landon.
等等  拉斐  等等  拜托了
Wait, Raf, wait. Please.
别  别走  好吗  我
Don't-don't go. Okay, I...
我能帮上你的  我需要你
I can help you. I need you.
兰德勒需要你
Landon needs you.
我们必须得做点什么了  这也太尴尬了
We need to do something. This is embarrassing.
你怎么不用你的魔法了呢
Why have you stopped using your magic?
因为凯勒布这么说了
Because Kaleb said...
- 因为我父亲也这么说了  - 你的父亲
- Because my dad said... Your father
已经不是你的校长了
is no longer your headmaster.
我才是  而且我不像他
I am, and unlike him,
我从来没背叛过你的信任
I've never broken your trust.
所以或许你应该
So perhaps you ought
同样地把我说的话也权衡一下
to take what I say with the same consideration.
- 你想让我怎么做  - 再得一分就能打平了
- What do you want me to do?  - One more score
继续加油
ties it. Keep it up!
摇滚吧
* Rock it... *
好消息
Great news.
那个叫丹尼斯的孩子出现了
That kid Dennis turned up.
虽说心情不太好  但总体来说还算乖的了
A little hungover, but otherwise safe and sound,
所以  我想我该回去找找那几条失踪的狗了
so I guess I'll go back to looking for those missing dogs.
好吧  你来得刚刚好  你的儿子刚刚可来了个
Well, you're here just in time. Your son's leading
漂亮的翻盘呢
one hell of a comeback.
我还不知道伊森也上场了
Oh, I didn't think Ethan was playing.
上啊  加油啊  大家
Go! Come on, guys!
进到最佳的状态  摇滚吧
* Get in the groove, rock it *
好好鞭笞自己  让自己的身体动起来吧
* Just whip it good, so your body can move... *
准备
Pink 21!
好好鞭笞自己
* Just whip it good... *
准备  开始
Blue 48! Hut!
所有人  放松吧
* Everybody, let loose *
干扰咒
Tenebris lapsus.
我天
Oh, my God.
- 天呐  - 他没事吧
- Oh, God.  - Is he okay?
宝贝  宝贝  宝贝  快过来  没事的  深呼吸
Babe, babe, babe, come here, it's okay, just breathe,
亲爱的
sweetheart, just... Hey.
找医生来
Get a medic!
你他妈都干了什么
What the hell did you do?
你是在为这个不幸的意外责怪我吗
Are you blaming me for this unfortunate accident?
人类的身体这么脆弱又不是我的错
It's not my fault the human body is so frail.
闭嘴吧你  别装作一副置身事外的样子  盖瑞·波宾斯
Stop it. Stop pretending that you're above it, Gary Poppins.
我看到你把什么东西给乔茜了
I saw you give something to Josie.
如果让我知道你跟这件事有关系
If I find out you had some part in this...
那她肯定会告诉你的  你说是不是
She'd tell you. Wouldn't she?
不管怎么说  她还是你女儿嘛
She's your daughter, after all.
没错  你最好记清楚了
That's right. And don't you forget it.
就算有人忘记了什么  那也是她
If anyone has something to forget, it's her.
以及你之前所有的那些学生
And all the rest of your former students.
对于他们来说  被一个这样喜欢颐指气使的权威人物当作
It must have been traumatic to have their authority figure
动物园里的动物对待  一定得留下创伤吧
treat them like animals in a zoo.
你所说根本不属实
That is not what happened.
不是这样吗
Isn't it?
恐怕咱们思想上的鸿沟
I fear the gap in our ideologies
是无法跨越的了  萨尔茨曼校长
cannot be bridged, Principal Saltzman.
我不得不禁止你再踏入这个校园一步
I must ask that you not set foot on this campus again.
毕竟我得保证我的学生们的安全嘛
For the sake of the students under my protection.
我女儿在这里上学
My daughters go to this school.
你不能这么做
You can't do that.
我就是这么做了
I just did.
当然  你也可以让他们去上公立学校嘛
Of course, you can always enroll them in public school.
但是如果你不那么自欺欺人的话
But if you're honest with yourself,
你应该知道最适合她们的地方就是这里  跟我一起
you know the best place for them is here, with me.
以及离你远点
And away from you.
别又是这样吧
Not again!
别打了
Break it up!
塞巴斯蒂安
Sebastian?
Sebastian.
伊丽莎白
Elizabeth.
你是在跟踪我吗
Are you following me?
我跟你说了  大家基本上都叫我丽兹的
I told you. Most people call me Lizzie.
我又不是大家
I am not most people.
所以我才告诉你  我们俩是不可能再继续下去了
Which is why I told you we cannot go down this path.
但是你从来没解释过原因
But you never explained why.
然后你又突然出现在比赛上  抱歉
And then you showed up at the game, and I'm sorry,
但是也算是男人的经典套路了
but that is a typical dude move.
我必须再见你一面
I had to see you again.
你让我回想起了我之前认识的一个人
You remind me of someone I used to know.
这我可不好说
I don't know.
我还算挺特立独行的
I'm pretty unique.
没错  她也是
Yes. As was she.
我曾经认为她
I once thought that she
是我所见的人中最美丽年轻的女人了
was the most beautiful young woman I would ever see.
你觉得那句话同样适用于我吗
Is that line supposed to work on me?
无论如何  那是一条
Either way, it is a line
- 我们无法逾越的界限  - 为什么不可以
- that we cannot cross.  - Why not?
这次你可别再给我打哑谜了
And no riddles this time.
因为你给我下了咒  伊丽莎白
Because you bewitch me, Elizabeth.
那不是当然的吗  我是女巫啊
Well, duh. I'm a witch.
你是怪物吗
Are you a monster?
是的
Yes.
我是个吸血鬼
I am a vampyr.
夜的使者
Creature of the night.
谢天谢地
Oh, thank God.
我有点疑惑了
Uh, um... I'm a bit confused.
我也是  我还以为你是什么北海巨妖啥的
So was I. I thought you were, like, a kraken or something.
但是这不重要了
But this is no big deal.
我有一些好朋友也是吸血鬼
Some of my best friends are vampires.
那我们俩就只能  是朋友了么
Are we to just be... friends, then?
不  因为我的朋友可不能这么做
No. Because friends don't get to do this...
霍普  不
Hope? No!
拉斐
Raf.
兰  它还没死呢
Lan, it's not done!
我以为你已经走了
I thought you were gone.
你可以不用再想了  兄弟  因为我回来了
You can stop thinking it, bro, 'cause I'm back.
多亏了你  兄弟
Thanks to you, man.
不  是她  是她
No, it was, it was her, she...
她救了我们俩  什么
She saved us both. What--
那个女孩是谁
Who was that girl?
关于独来独往  只能说这是无法永远持续下去的状态
The thing about being alone is that it can never last.
爸  爸
Dad! Dad!
海上的波浪
* Waves on the ocean *
沙滩上的爱心
* Hearts in the sand... *
在某些时刻
At some point,
我们都需要走出自己的小天地去寻求安慰
we all need to reach out and find comfort.
首先  寻求我们所熟悉的
At first, to what we know:
那些人  那些地方
the people, the places,
事物原本的样子
how everything used to be.
恩典洗涤了你的内心
* Grace washing over you *
所以今晚挽留住你亲爱的人
* So hold the ones you love tonight *
别放手  别眨眼
* Don't let go, don't blink *
放松点  停下来  因为时间将会
* Easy. Stop.  'Cause time is gonna *
与你擦肩而过
* Pass you by... *
但事情都会变的  无论你怎么做
But things change. And no matter what you do,
都不会回到从前了
it's never gonna be the same.
急诊中心
所以那个问题便成了  你会去哪
So the question becomes, where do you go?
你要做什么
What do you do?
倘若我们只能拥有此刻  霍普
* What if all we have is now? * Hope?
你在这里做什么
What are you doing here?
我只是  我就想看看
I just, I wanted to see how
你和伊森比赛之后怎么样了
you and Ethan were doing after the game.
他为了奖学金做了那么多的努力
He worked so hard for that scholarship.
现在全完了
And now it's over.
或许只要在你还在探索目标的旅途中时  这些都不重要
Maybe it doesn't matter as long as you go somewhere.
世间万物终将归为尘土
* Billions of miles will fade into dust... *
拉斐怎么样了
Hey. How's Raf?
所以今晚挽留住你亲爱的人吧
* So hold the ones you love tonight *
还在调整
Adjusting.
别放手  别眨眼
* Don't let go, don't blink... *
我现在不知道说什么
That's... more than I can say.
我不知道为什么我会这样
I don't know why I'm acting like this.
我感觉  我讲不清楚  深埋在我体内的某个东西
I feel like, I don't know, something inside me
仿佛消失了
is just off.
时间总是滴答滴答地走过
* It's always ticking down... *
听起来咱们俩这一天都过得够呛的
Sounds like we both had a day.
你先开口还是我先开口
You want to go first or should I?
倘若我们只能拥有此时呢
* What if all we have is now? *
在你离开比赛之后
After you left the game...
我做了件很可怕的事
I did something horrible.
我伤害了某人
I hurt someone.
而且我认为  我确实是想这么做的
And I think I wanted to.
所以挽留住你爱的人吧
* So hold the ones you love... *
无论你做了什么
Whatever you did,
要是我早听了你的话  那件事都不会发生
it wouldn't have happened if I'd just listened to you.
别眨眼  因为
* Don't blink, 'cause *
时间将会
* Time is gonna... *
霍普的事情上你是对的
You were right about Hope.
橄榄球比赛上的那个女孩吗
The girl from the football game?
她绝对不是她所说的那个人
She's definitely not who she says she is.
她是谁
Who is she?
我还希望你能帮助我一起查清楚
I was kind of hoping you'd help me figure it out.
还有很多其他的事情也是
Along with a bunch of other stuff, too.
什么事情
Like what?
怪物们回来了
The monsters are back.
我不知道这是怎么一回事  我也不知道能否阻止这一切
I have no idea how or why, or if it's gonna stop.
我只知道我之前无论对马里瓦尔做了什么
All I know is that whatever I did to take down Malivore,
都无济于事  现在我觉得
it didn't work, and now I think
那些怪物都在冲着我来  而且
the monsters are coming after me, and...
挽留住你亲爱的人吧
* Hold the ones you love *
就今晚
* Tonight *
别放手
* Don't let go... *
但是唯独能够见你
But seeing you is the only thing
才能让我在挺过这些糟心的事情中让自己感觉好点
that's making me feel a little bit better about any of this.
我现在真的很想亲吻你
I'd really like to kiss you now.
时间永远在滴答滴答地逝去
* It's always ticking down. *
兰德勒
Landon...
无论那些马里瓦尔的
whatever monsters
怪物们有什么通天的本领
are coming for you from Malivore,
想挨你一下  都必须得先过了我这种力量强大
are gonna have to go through a very powerful witch
还有点愤怒控制问题的女巫这关
who apparently has anger issues.
我不会让他们伤你分毫的
I'm not gonna let them get you.
好吗  我保证
Okay? I promise.
Xgun擦枪小组 有偿招募译制成员 诚邀阁下
加入Q群：545053435
请注明职务：翻译、听译、aegisub特效（熟练手）
另：招募长期居住加拿大、美国的童鞋帮忙录制CC字幕（有偿）
■
人人视频APP
美剧、韩剧、日剧
离线高清缓存
支持电视投屏
各大应用商店均可下载
在线看美剧的追剧神器